ibancalculator.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy

## 1\. An overview of data protection

### General

The following gives a simple overview of what happens to your personal information when you visit our website. Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified. Detailed information on the subject of data protection can be found in our privacy policy found below.

### Data collection on our website

**Who is responsible for the data collection on this website?**

The data collected on this website are processed by the website operator. The operator's contact details can be found in the website's required legal notice.

**How do we collect your data?**

Some data are collected when you provide it to us. This could, for example, be data you enter on a contact form, a search form, or an IBAN validation or conversion form.

Other data are collected automatically by our IT systems when you visit the website. These data are primarily technical data such as the browser and operating system you are using or when you accessed the page. These data are collected automatically as soon as you enter our website.

**What do we use your data for?**

Part of the data is collected to ensure the proper functioning of the website. For instance, search queries are used for performing searches, IBANs are validated, and domestic account numbers are converted to IBANs. The IBANs you enter are not used for any purpose which does not serve the functioning of this website. In particular, they are not shared with third parties. Other data can be used to analyze how visitors use the site.

**What rights do you have regarding your data?**

You always have the right to request information about your stored data, its origin, its recipients, and the purpose of its collection at no charge. You also have the right to request that it be corrected, blocked, or deleted. You can contact us at any time using the address given in the legal notice if you have further questions about the issue of privacy and data protection. You may also, of course, file a complaint with the competent regulatory authorities.

## 2\. General information and mandatory information

### Data protection

The operators of this website take the protection of your personal data very seriously. We treat your personal data as confidential and in accordance with the statutory data protection regulations and this privacy policy.

If you use this website, various pieces of personal data will be collected. Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified. This privacy policy explains what information we collect and what we use it for. It also explains how and for what purpose this happens.

Please note that data transmitted via the internet (e.g. via email communication) may be subject to security breaches. Complete protection of your data from third-party access is not possible.

### Notice concerning the party responsible for this website

The party responsible for processing data on this website is:

Theano GmbH  
Kiefernweg 8  
49205 Hasbergen  
Deutschland

Telephone: +49-5405-92825432  
Email: info@theano.de

The responsible party is the natural or legal person who alone or jointly with others decides on the purposes and means of processing personal data (names, email addresses, etc.).

### Revocation of your consent to the processing of your data

Many data processing operations are only possible with your express consent. You may revoke your consent at any time with future effect. An informal email making this request is sufficient. The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed.

### Right to file complaints with regulatory authorities

If there has been a breach of data protection legislation, the person affected may file a complaint with the competent regulatory authorities. The competent regulatory authority for matters related to data protection legislation is the data protection officer of the German state in which our company is headquartered. A list of data protection officers and their contact details can be found at the following link: <https://www.bfdi.bund.de/DE/Infothek/Anschriften_Links/anschriften_links-node.html>.

### SSL or TLS encryption

This site uses SSL or TLS encryption for security reasons and for the protection of the transmission of confidential content, such as the inquiries you send to us as the site operator. You can recognize an encrypted connection in your browser's address line when it changes from "http://" to "https://" and the lock icon is displayed in your browser's address bar.

If SSL or TLS encryption is activated, the data you transfer to us cannot be read by third parties.

### Encrypted payments on this website

If you enter into a contract which requires you to send us your payment information (e.g. account number for direct debits), we will require this data to process your payment.

Payment transactions using common means of payment (Visa/MasterCard, direct debit) are only made via encrypted SSL or TLS connections. You can recognize an encrypted connection in your browser's address line when it changes from "http://" to "https://" and the lock icon in your browser line is visible.

In the case of encrypted communication, any payment details you submit to us cannot be read by third parties.

### Information, blocking, deletion

As permitted by law, you have the right to be provided at any time with information free of charge about any of your personal data that is stored as well as its origin, the recipient and the purpose for which it has been processed. You also have the right to have this data corrected, blocked or deleted. You can contact us at any time using the address given in our legal notice if you have further questions on the topic of personal data.

### Opposition to promotional emails

We hereby expressly prohibit the use of contact data published in the context of website legal notice requirements with regard to sending promotional and informational materials not expressly requested. The website operator reserves the right to take specific legal action if unsolicited advertising material, such as email spam, is received.

## 3\. Data protection officer

If you want a quick reply to a data protection-related request, please send a mail to: [privacy@theano.de](mailto:privacy@theano.de) . But you are also free to contact our external data protection officer.

Data protection officer:

Legaltrust GmbH  
Contact person: Herr Michael Michalak  
Lietzenburger Str. 94  
10719 Berlin  
Germany   
Tel. 030 / 887 27 609  
Fax. 030 / 887 27 606  
E-Mail: datenschutz@prive.eu 

## 4\. Data collection on our website

### Cookies

Some of our web pages use cookies. Cookies do not harm your computer and do not contain any viruses. Cookies help make our website more user-friendly, efficient, and secure. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer and saved by your browser.

Most of the cookies we use are so-called "session cookies." They are automatically deleted after your visit. Other cookies remain in your device's memory until you delete them. These cookies make it possible to recognize your browser when you next visit the site.

You can configure your browser to inform you about the use of cookies so that you can decide on a case-by-case basis whether to accept or reject a cookie. Alternatively, your browser can be configured to automatically accept cookies under certain conditions or to always reject them, or to automatically delete cookies when closing your browser. Disabling cookies may limit the functionality of this website.

Cookies which are necessary to allow electronic communications or to provide certain functions you wish to use (such as the shopping cart) are stored pursuant to Art. 6 paragraph 1, letter f of DSGVO. The website operator has a legitimate interest in the storage of cookies to ensure an optimized service provided free of technical errors. If other cookies (such as those used to analyze your surfing behavior) are also stored, they will be treated separately in this privacy policy.

### Server log files

The website provider automatically collects and stores information that your browser automatically transmits to us in "server log files". These are:

  * Browser type and browser version
  * Operating system used
  * Referrer URL
  * Host name of the accessing computer
  * Time of the server request
  * IP address

These data will not be combined with data from other sources.

The basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) (b) DSGVO, which allows the processing of data to fulfill a contract or for measures preliminary to a contract.

### Registration on this website

You can register on our website in order to access additional functions offered here. The input data will only be used for the purpose of using the respective site or service for which you have registered. The mandatory information requested during registration must be provided in full. Otherwise, we will reject your registration.

To inform you about important changes such as those within the scope of our site or technical changes, we will use the email address specified during registration.

We will process the data provided during registration only based on your consent per Art. 6 (1)(a) DSGVO. You may revoke your consent at any time with future effect. An informal email making this request is sufficient. The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed.

We will continue to store the data collected during registration for as long as you remain registered on our website. Statutory retention periods remain unaffected.

### Processing of data (customer and contract data)

We collect, process, and use personal data only insofar as it is necessary to establish, or modify legal relationships with us (master data). This is done based on Art. 6 (1) (b) DSGVO, which allows the processing of data to fulfill a contract or for measures preliminary to a contract. We collect, process and use your personal data when accessing our website (usage data) only to the extent required to enable you to access our service or to bill you for the same.

Collected customer data shall be deleted after completion of the order or termination of the business relationship. Legal retention periods remain unaffected.

### Data transferred when signing up for services and digital content

We transmit personally identifiable data to third parties only to the extent required to fulfill the terms of your contract with us, for example, to banks entrusted to process your payments.

Your data will not be transmitted for any other purpose unless you have given your express permission to do so. Your data will not be disclosed to third parties for advertising purposes without your express consent.

The basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) (b) DSGVO, which allows the processing of data to fulfill a contract or for measures preliminary to a contract.

## 5\. Analytics and advertising

### Matomo (formerly Piwik)

This website uses the open source web analytics service Matomo. Matomo uses so-called "cookies". These are text files that are stored on your computer and that allow an analysis of the use of the website by you. For this purpose, the information generated by the cookie about the use of this website is stored on our server. The IP address is anonymized before it is stored.

Matomo cookies remain on your device until you delete them.

The storage of Matomo cookies is based on Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO. The website operator has a legitimate interest in analyzing user behavior in order to optimize both its website and its advertising.

The information generated by the cookies about your use of this website will not be disclosed to third parties. You can prevent these cookies being stored by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser. However, we wish to point out that doing so may mean you will not be able to enjoy the full functionality of this website.

If you do not agree with the storage and use of your data, you can disable this feature here. In this case, an opt-out cookie will be stored in your browser to prevent Matomo from storing your usage data. If you delete your cookies, this will mean that the opt-out cookie will also be deleted. You will then need to reactivate it when you return to our site if you wish your activity not to be tracked.

### Google AdSense

This website uses Google AdSense, a service for including advertisements from Google Inc. ("Google"). It is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.

Google AdSense uses so-called "cookies", which are text files stored in your computer that enable an analysis of the way you use the website. Google AdSense also uses so-called web beacons (invisible graphics). Through these web beacons, information such as the visitor traffic on these pages can be evaluated.

The information generated by cookies and web beacons relating to your use of this website (including your IP address), and delivery of advertising formats, is transmitted to a Google server in the US and stored there. This information can be passed on from Google to contracting parties of Google. However, Google will not merge your IP address with other data you have stored.

AdSense cookies are stored based on Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO. The website operator has a legitimate interest in analyzing user behavior to optimize both its website and its advertising.

You can prevent the installation of cookies by setting your browser software accordingly. Please be aware that in this case, you may not be able to make full use of all the features of this website. By using this website, you agree to the processing of data relating to you and collected by Google as described and for the purposes set out above.

More information about Google can be found in their privacy statement: <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites?hl=en>

### Netpoint Media

Some of the ads on this website are influenced using cookies from Netpoint Media GmbH Rheinallee 60  
55283 Nierstein  
You can find out more about this company and opt out of their cookies here: [www.netpoint-media.de/technik/datenschutz](http://www.netpoint-media.de/technik/datenschutz). 

### MSO Digital

Some of our ad impressions are monetized via [MSO Digital](https://www.mso-digital.de/datenschutz/?utm_source=Yield+DSGVO&utm_campaign=376b0f1b70-EMAIL_CAMPAIGN_2018_05_07&utm_medium=email&utm_term=0_6fd3f61f4f-376b0f1b70-170733557), who in turn work with [ these (changing) partners](https://www.mso-digital.de/yield-management/dsgvo/?utm_source=Yield+DSGVO&utm_campaign=376b0f1b70-EMAIL_CAMPAIGN_2018_05_07&utm_medium=email&utm_term=0_6fd3f61f4f-376b0f1b70-170733557). MSO Digital is registered at:  
MSO Digital GmbH & Co. KG  
Erich-Maria-Remarque-Ring 14  
49074 Osnabrück  
Germany 

### Tisoomi

We also cooperate with tisoomi-services (a service by tisoomi GmbH, Gänsemarkt 31, 20354 Hamburg). tisoomi uses cookies for targeting ads. The data about your use of this website which tisoomi collects with its cookies (including your IP address) is processed and stored (after pseudo-anonymizing it) on a server in Germany. tisoomi uses this information for optimizing the ads display and for generating reports for the publisher. You can opt out of cookies by configuring your browser accordingly. By using this website, you declare that you agree to the data processing by tisoomi as described here. You can opt out of tisoomi's interest-based ad targeting at any time here: https://www.tisoomi-services.com/datasecurity 

### Yieldlove

_We also use Yieldlove as advertising partner. In the Yieldlove section below, "we" refers to Yieldlove, not Theano GmbH._

Yieldlove delivers advertising banners on behalf of its customers. All our banners use cookies. We place these banners on third-party websites, such as a news page, with the help of third-party providers.

For diagnostic purposes, troubleshooting, and detecting fraudulent behavior, we collect user information in cookies using our 6-month lifecycle. The captured user information includes user agent, device, HTTP referrer and the IP. This data is not retained for more than 7 days.

Yieldlove takes reasonable steps to protect any information we process from misuse, loss, unauthorized access, modification or notification. We take physical, electronic and procedural security measures to protect the data we process. By doing so, we restrict access to this information to authorized employees.

For the cookies that our third-party advertisers place for advertising purposes, we refer to the disclaimers that they have provided on the topic on their own websites. Note that we can only refer to these disclaimers, as they change regularly and Yieldlove has no control over them.

THIRD PARTIES AND OPT-OUT

A central contradiction possibility for different third-party suppliers in particular US-companies is also attainable under the following link: optout.networkadvertising.org But you can also opt-out separately for each company we work with. Responsible for the data collection and for the delivery of interest based-based online advertising are the following companies on behalf of Yieldlove GmbH:

_4w Marketplace_

4w Marketplace (www.4wmarketplace.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of 4w Marketplace is 4w Marketplace srl located in Fisciano (Salerno) – 84084 in Via Giovanni Paolo II n.100. In case you would like to prevent 4w Marketplace from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: [http://www.4wmarketplace.com/privacy/](http://www.4wmarketplace.com/privacy/)

Opt-out: <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/it/le-tue-scelte>

_Adform_

Adform (www.adform.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Adform is Adform located in Wildersgade 10B, 1, 1408 Copenhagen, Denmark. In case you would like to prevent Adform from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: _[https://site.adform.com/privacy-policy-opt-out/](https://site.adform.com/privacy-policy-opt-out/)_

Opt-out: _[https://site.adform.com/privacy-policy-opt-out/](https://site.adform.com/privacy-policy-opt-out/)_

_Amazon_

Amazon (https://www.aps.amazon.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Amazon publisher services is Amazon publisher services located in Washington – 410 Terry Ave. North, Seattle, WA 98109-5210. In case you would like to prevent Amazon publisher services from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: [https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=hp_left_sib?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=hp_left_sib?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496)

Opt-out: [https://www.amazon.com/adprefs/ref=hp_468496_advertisingpref2](https://www.amazon.com/adprefs/ref=hp_468496_advertisingpref2)

_AppNexus_

AppNexus (https://www.appnexus.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of AppNexus is AppNexus Group located in in New York – 28 W. 23rd Street, New York, New York, 10010. In case you would like to prevent Appnexus from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/privacy-policy

Opt-out: https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy#choices

_Conversant_

Conversant (https://www.conversantmedia.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Conversant is Conversant inc. located in in Chicago (IL) – 101 North Wacker, 23rd Floor Chicago, IL 60606. In case you would like to prevent Conversant from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <http://www.conversantmedia.com/legal/privacy>

Opt-out: http://optout.conversantmedia.com/

_Criteo_

Criteo (https://www.criteo.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Criteo is Criteo located in Paris – 32 Rue Blanche – 75009 Paris - France. In case you would like to prevent Criteo from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: http://www.criteo.com/privacy/

Opt-out: https://www.criteo.com/privacy/

District M

District M (https://districtm.net) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of District M is District M located in Montreal – 5455 Gaspe Ave #730, Montreal, QC H2T 3B3, Canada. In case you would like to prevent District M from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <https://districtm.net/en/page/platforms-data-and-privacy-policy/>

Opt-out: [https://cdn.districtm.ca/optout.html](https://cdn.districtm.ca/optout.html)

Doubleclick

Doubleclick (www.doubleclickbygoogle.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Doubleclick is Google located in Ireland Limited, Gordon House, Barrow St Dublin 4 Ireland. In case you would like to prevent Doubleclick from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/

Opt-out: [https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en)

Facebook

Facebook (www.facebook.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Facebook is Facebook Inc., located in 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. In case you would like to prevent Facebook from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: www.facebook.com/full_data_use_policy

Opt-out: www.facebook.com/ads/preferences

Indexexchange

Indexexchange (www.indexexchange.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Indexexchange is Indexexchange located in New York – 20 W 22nd St. Suite 1101, New York, NY 10010\. In case you would like to prevent Indexexchange from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <http://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/>

Opt-out: http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/

Media.net

Media.net (http://www.media.net/privacy-policy) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Media.net is Media.net Advertising Ltd. located in Dubai – 107/108, DIC Building 5, Dubai Internet City, Dubai, 215028, United Arab Emirates. In case you would like to prevent Media.net from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: http://www.media.net/privacy-policy

Opt-out: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>

_Oath_

Oath (https://www.oath.com/) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Oath is Oath (EMEA) Limited located in Dublin - 5-7 Point Square, North Wall Quay. In case you would like to prevent Oath from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: [http://privacy.aol.com/](http://privacy.aol.com/)

Opt-out: https://aim.yahoo.com/aim/ie/en/optout/

OpenX

OpenX (https://www.OpenX.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of OpenX is OpenX located in Pasadena – 888 E Walnut St, 2nd Floor, Pasadena CA, 91101, USA. In case you would like to prevent OpenX from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: https://www.openx.com/de_de/privacy-policy/

Opt-out: <https://www.openx.com/legal/interest-based-advertising/>

Pubmatic

Pubmatic (https://www.pubmatic.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Pubmatic is Pubmatic, Inc. located in Redwood City – 305 Main Street, First Floor, Redwood City, California 94063, USA. In case you would like to prevent Pubmatic from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: https://www.openx.com/de_de/privacy-policy/

Opt-out: https://pubmatic.com/legal/opt-out/

Pulsepoint

Pulsepoint (https://www.pulsepoint.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Pulsepoint is Pulsepoint, Inc. located in New York – 360 Madison Avenue, 14th Floor, New York, NY 10017. In case you would like to prevent Pulsepoint from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <https://www.pulsepoint.com/privacy-policy>

Opt-out: http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/

Reachnet

Reachnet (https://www.reachnet.de) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Reachnet is Reachnet DE Ltd. located in Hamburg – Grindelallee 41, D-20146 Hamburg. In case you would like to prevent Reachnet from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: http://www.reachnet.de/unternehmen/agb.html

Opt-out: [https://adfarm1.adition.com/opt?m=optout&n=73](https://adfarm1.adition.com/opt?m=optout&n=73)

Rubicon Project

Rubicon Project (https://www.rubiconproject.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Rubicon Project is Rubicon Project, inc. located in Playa Vista – 12181 Bluff Creek Drive, 4th Floor, Playa Vista, CA 90094, USA. In case you would like to prevent Rubicon Project from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: http://www.rubiconproject.com/privacy-policy/

Opt-out: <https://rubiconproject.com/privacy/consumer-online-profile-and-opt-out/>

Primis

Primis (https://www.primis.tech) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Primis is Primis LTD located in 622 Third avenue, McCann New York House 10017 New York City, USA. In case you would like to prevent Primis from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: https://www.primis.tech/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/primisPrivacyPolicy2018.pdf

Opt-out: https://web.archive.org/web/20180116234711/http:/live.sekindo.com/utils/cookieOptOut.php

Smaato

Smaato (https://www.smaato.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Smaato is Smaato Ad Services located in Hamburg – Valentinskamp 70, Emporio, 20355 Hamburg, Germany. In case you would like to prevent Smaato from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <https://www.smaato.com/privacy/>

Opt-out: [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)

SmartAdserver

SmartAdserver (https://www.smartadserver.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of SmartAdserver is SmartAdserver located in Paris – 66 Rue de la Chaussée d´Antin, 75009 Paris, France. In case you would like to prevent SmartAdserver from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: http://smartadserver.com/company/privacy-policy/

Opt-out: http://www.smartadserver.com/diffx/optout/IABOptout.aspx

Sovrn

Sovrn (https://www.sovrn.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Sovrn is Sovrn Holdings, Inc. located in Boulder – 5541 Central Avenue, Boulder, CO 80301. In case you would like to prevent Sovrn from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy-eu/>

Opt-out: https://info.evidon.com/pub_info/15620?v=1&nt=0&nw=false

_Ströer SSP_

Ströer SSP (https://www.adscale.de) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Ströer SSP is Ströer media Deutschland GmbH located in Köln – 50999 Köln, Ströer-Allee 1\. In case you would like to prevent Adscale from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <http://www.adscale.de/datenschutz>

Opt-out: ih.adscale.de/adscale-ih/oo

Twiago

Twiago (https://www.twiago.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Twiago is Twiago located in Köln – Gustav-Heinemann-Ufer 72b, 50968 Köln. In case you would like to prevent Twiago from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: http://www.twiago.com/datenschutz/

Opt-out: http://control.twiago.com/privacy.php?lang=0

Mopub

Mopub (https://www.mopub.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Mopub is Twitter, Inc. located in San Francisco – 1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, Ca 94103. In case you would like to prevent Moppub from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: https://www.mopub.com/legal/privacy/

Opt-out: https://www.mopub.com/legal/privacy/

Inmobi

Inmobi (https://www.inmobi.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Inmobi is Inmobi Pte Ltd located in Bangalore – Embassy Tech Square, Kadubeesanahalli Village Outer Ring Road, Varthur Hobli, Bangalore 560103. In case you would like to prevent Inmobi from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <https://www.inmobi.com/privacy-policy/>

Opt-out: https://www.inmobi.com/page/opt-out/

OTHER / UNFORESEEN COOKIES

Due to the way in which Internet and websites work, it is possible that we do not always have oversight into the cookies that are placed through our banners by third parties. This is particularly the case when our banners contain embedded elements such as texts, documents, images or film clips that are stored by another party, but that are shown on, in or through our banners.

Should you encounter cookies on this website that fall into this category which we have not mentioned above, please let us know or contact the third party directly and ask which cookies they have placed, what the reason for this is, what the lifetime of the cookie is and in what way they have safeguarded your privacy.

YOUR RIGHTS WITH REGARDS TO YOUR DATA

Yieldlove does not view the banner advertising data it uses as personal data under the applicable law. Likewise, we do not collect or process sensitive personal data such as data on racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, health, or sex life. We also do not knowingly collect data from children under the age of 12.

However, if you want to correct, update or delete the banner advertising data we have, or if you would like to correct, update or delete the personal data that you have provided to us via the contact form on our homepage, you can contact us by e-mail at  _[datenschutzbeauftragter@stroeer.de](mailto:datenschutzbeauftragter@stroeer.de)_.

EDAA

We participate in the European Digital Advertising Alliance (EDAA) self-regulatory programs and adhere to the  _[EDAA Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising](http://www.edaa.eu/european-principles/)_. EDAA principally acts as the central licensing body for the OBA Icon and provides technical means for consumers to exercise transparency and control over OBA through the youronlinechoices.eu online consumer choice platform. EDAA is governed by EU-level organisations which make up the value chain of OBA within Europe and acts to ensure European consistency in approach. Click  _[here](http://www.edaa.eu/)_  to learn more about the EDAA.

MODIFICATIONS AND CONTACT

We will, on occasion need to adapt these statements. For instance, if we modify our website or if the rules governing cookies or privacy change. We or our partners may always modify the content of the statements and the cookies that are stated without prior warning. Please refer back to this web page to see the latest version.

In case you have any questions and/or comments, or wish to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at  _[datenschutzbeauftragter@stroeer.de](mailto:datenschutzbeauftragter@stroeer.de)_  or by writing to:

Yieldlove GmbH  
Kehrwieder 9  
20457 Hamburg  
Germany

### Opting out of cookies for advertising

You may change your privacy settings at any time.
